<NomaiObject>

  <TextBlock>
    <ID>1</ID>
    <Text>
      What can I learn from the signals in this system?
    </Text>
  </TextBlock>

  <TextBlock>
    <ID>2</ID>
    <Text>
      Found this signal next to a large green crystal. Was a hassle getting there, and all I got was another 4-digit code.
    </Text>
  </TextBlock>

  <TextBlock>
    <ID>3</ID>
    <Text>
      Signal found at a green fire. The 4-digit code it gave me didn't sound like other ones.
    </Text>
  </TextBlock>

  <TextBlock>
    <ID>4</ID>
    <Text>
      Thought I might try combining those two weird signals into a new 4-digit code, and it actually worked. Still completely useless to me, though.
    </Text>
  </TextBlock>
  
  <TextBlock>
    <ID>5</ID>
    <Text>
      Signal located next to an alien on a strange, shape-shifting moon. Not sure what they were doing there.
    </Text>
  </TextBlock>

  <TextBlock>
    <ID>6</ID>
    <Text>
      Found this signal deep underground at some sort of shrine. Gave me another 4-digit code, but this one sounded different than the others.
    </Text>
  </TextBlock>

  <TextBlock>
    <ID>7</ID>
    <Text>
      Signal found at a radio tower. There were some nice maps of the solar system inside, so I took one to put on the wall here.
    </Text>
  </TextBlock>

  <TextBlock>
    <ID>8</ID>
    <Text>
      My scans indicate this signal is in the center of the sun. Not sure how I'm supposed to reach it. I happened to catch a solar flare that carried part of the signal, but the eruption wasn't strong enough to carry the entire signal. I'll have to get things done without this one."
    </Text>
  </TextBlock>

  <TextBlock>
    <ID>9</ID>
    <Text>
      Found this signal on the structure oribiting the sun. Your average pilot might have trouble landing on something like that, but I'm not your average pilot.
    </Text>
  </TextBlock>

  <TextBlock>
    <ID>10</ID>
    <Text>
      Followed this signal into the weird vine planet. Found it at a large ship after a few close encounters.
    </Text>
  </TextBlock>
  
</NomaiObject>